

PROFILE

I am a Frontend Developer with 2 years of experience in creating user-friendly web applications. I specialize in team collaboration, bug resolution, and developing new features. I love what I do and am eager to learn new technologies and frameworks.

EDUCATION

2018 - 2022

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering
Holy Trinity College of General Santos City

2017 - 2018

Technical Vocational and Livelihood

Holy Trinity College of General Santos City | Senior High School

WORK EXPERIENCE

August 16, 2022 - Present

Biotech Fams Inc. | Banga, South Cotabato, Philippines

UI/UX DESIGNER / FRONT END DEVELOPER

- Maintained and optimized systems to ensure functionality and performance.
- Identified and resolved bugs promptly to enhance system reliability.
- Collaborated with teams to implement new features and enhancements.
- Developed comprehensive user guides for applications, enhancing user experience and reducing support queries.

November 2021 - April 2022

Virtual Assistant | Part-Time

Account Registration
Sale Executor

PERSONAL INFO

Email

merryglenpancho@gmail.com

Phone

+63 9458103766

Date of Birth

E September 08, 1999

Marital Status

Single

Address

O General Santos City Philippines

SKILLS

Teamwork

Problem Solving

Technical Skills

Software

Front-end Frameworks:

Vue.js, Angular.js

Design Tools:

Figma

Front-end Technologies:

- JavaScript
- HTML
- Bootstrap
- CSS
- Database Management

Software Development Tools

Jira

GitHub

Bitbucket

LANGUAGE

English

Tagalog

Cebuano